export const questions: {
  question: string;
  options: string[];
  answer: string;
}[] = [
  {
    question: "What is the past tense of 'to be'?",
    options: ["am", "is", "was/were", "will be"],
    answer: "was/were",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the third person singular of 'to be' in present?",
    options: ["are", "is", "was", "been"],
    answer: "is",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the past participle of 'to be'?",
    options: ["be", "is", "are", "been"],
    answer: "been",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the negative form of 'to be' in present?",
    options: ["am not/aren't/isn't", "are not", "is not", "weren't"],
    answer: "am not/aren't/isn't",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you form the future tense of 'to be'?",
    options: ["is", "was", "am", "will be"],
    answer: "will be",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a correct sentence?",
    options: [
      "He are happy.",
      "They am working.",
      "She is dancing.",
      "I is here.",
    ],
    answer: "She is dancing.",
  },
  {
    question: "Which sentence uses 'to be' in the past tense?",
    options: [
      "She is going to the park.",
      "They were at the party.",
      "I am playing soccer.",
      "We are studying.",
    ],
    answer: "They were at the party.",
  },
  {
    question: "Which form of 'to be' is used for 'I' in present tense?",
    options: ["are", "is", "was", "am"],
    answer: "am",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct form of 'to be' for 'They' in past tense?",
    options: ["are", "was", "were", "is"],
    answer: "were",
  },
  {
    question: "Complete the sentence: 'I ___ going to the store.'",
    options: ["are", "am", "is", "were"],
    answer: "am",
  },
];
